PRAMOD N

Mob: +91 7795716108

npramod95@gmail.com

PROFILE

Accomplished software engineer specializing in object-oriented approaches to web development. Extensive background in full life-cycle of software development process including requirements gathering, design, coding, testing, debugging, deployment and maintenance.

Proven track record of designing and implementing flexible solutions which support frequent UI and functionality changes.

TECHNICAL SKILL SET

Technologies : Angular 2/4, React.js, Redux, HTML, CSS, JavaScript,

JQuery

Databases : Postgres, MySQL **Operating Systems** : UNIX/ Linux, Windows

Web and Application Servers : Apache
Version Control Tools : Git
Build Tools : npm

WORK EXPERIENCE SUMMARY

Software Engineer

Udaan(Innoventes Technologies), Bangalore - July, 2019 to Present

- Contributed the functionalities for Udaan Console Development and Udaan Logistics Development
- Developed Facility creation functionality.
- Added the functionalities for Udaan Credit Application.

Software Engineer

Lemnisk(Innoventes Technologies), Bangalore - Jan, 2019 to July, 2019

- Developed 4 responsive demo-websites for the implementation and displaying of how the product executes.
- Took care of placing the product in the Client Websites by writing and placing the scripts.
- Contributed 4 Modules for the Product site. Added D3 Charts for displaying the visitors graph and clicks.

Software Engineer

Electem Business Solutions, Bangalore - Nov, 2017 to Dec, 2018

- Responsible for analyzing the requirement and developing front end and back end solution..
- Programming front and back end services as per the design and requirement.
- Resolve QA bugs.

- Critical support for the enhancements delivered.
- Bug fixing for the delivery made and production issues in other modules.
- Coordinating with various teams during staging.
- Demo with client on the deliverables for each sprint.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

- Bachelor of Engineering (BE) in Information Science & Engineering (ISE) from Dayananda Sagar College Of Engineering, Bangalore, India in April 2017.
- PUC (10+2) from **Sri Vidyabharathi Ind PU College, Shimoga, Karnataka**, India in April 2013.
- SSLC (10) from **Poorna Prajna Education Center, Bhadravati**, Karnataka, India in March 2011.